Ilene Wilkins

2214 Sea Island Dr. Dallas, Texas 75232- Cell #682-400-6087 | Ilenewilkins124@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A determined, self-motivated, and assertive professional with over thirty solid years of progressive management, training and development experience within property management. Talent for cultivating and supporting tenant relationships, leading to high occupancy rates, minimal turnover, and renewal of long-term leases.

EXPERIENCE

Lynd Mgmt, Winn Residential, Tipton Asset Group, Para West, Centra Partners Mgmt, Arlington, TX *Property Management/Account Manager/Leasing Professional* 2011 - 2019

- - Tax Credit
- - Developed and updated weekly marketing strategies
- - Responsible for collecting and depositing large amounts of rent
- - Familiar with eviction processes due to non-payment of rent
- - Supervised and scheduled 3-5 maintenance and office staffs' daily activities
- - Made appointments for sales closing
- Responsible for maintaining apartment upkeep and curbside appeal

Girling Home Health Care *Healthcare provider*

Dallas, TX **2010 - 2011**

- - Enhanced quality of life for positive living situations
- - Developed and updated weekly meal planning
- Responsible for charting vitals for patient's well-being
- - Familiar with hygiene upkeep

Tunder Property LLC/New World Realty *Community Manager*

Dallas, TX **2007 - 2010**

- - Managed and tracked supplies, orders on a computer
- - Prepared cash receipts after establishments close, and make bank deposits
- - Developed ability to work with diverse staff and clientele
- - Organized your work, multitask

EDUCATION

Kaplan Real Estate School (Business/Pre-Licensed Real Estate)

CAM I and CAM II

Eastfield College

Mesquite, TX 1996 - 1997

Central Business College

Texarkana, TX 1972 - 1973

Proficient in Microsoft Office Suite: Word; Excel; PowerPoint Business Management Software: Management Reports Incorporated (MRI); AMSI; Yardi; One – Site: Tax-Credit